Workbook, Grade 8, Book A, Unit 1, Page 123 B1.
Kitty, David and Nora are talking about friends.
Listen to their conversation and complete the notes below.
I think friends are very important to everyone.
Yes, I think so too.
When we're sad, friends give us love and care.
When we're happy, we can share our joy with them.
Yes, I agree.
If we don't have any friends, we may feel very lonely.
I also think a friend in need is a friend indeed.
A true friend will help us when things are difficult. That's right.
We should always be ready to help our friends.
And we should thank our friends when they help us. True.
We should make as many friends as we can.
Having more friends can make us happier.
Yes, and friends should always be kind, honest and helpful.
I believe that good friends will help us be like that too.